[MARIELA] Where are you going?
Why are you all dressed up?
To my new job, Ma.
Really? Someone hired you?
[ABI] Ms. Camille!
I have an idea for Pebblng.
[BILLY] When a couple meets on LoveList
and reaches marriage,
we celebrate it
as the ultimate validation
of our platform.
LoveFeast.
Turning meaningful connections
into lifelong commitments.
Well done, Abi.
I need someone like you here at Pebblng.
[LINDSAY] I really love the concept.
But, apparently, it's a replica
of an existing concept.
I'm here for Camille.
Please tell her it's Billy.
- I'm sure she knows me.
- Okay.
[ABI] Thank you, Ms. Camille,
for liking my concept.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[CAMILLE] But…
I think we need to change
the color scheme.
Because it should be
Pebblng's brand colors.
You uploaded LoveList's colors.
Ms. Billy…
Billy!
Oh my God, it's been forever!
What are you doing here?
Camille, we have to talk.
But I'll handle this first.
You have a lot to explain, Abi.
How did you get your hands
on our LoveFeast concept?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ABI SCOFFS]
Your concept?
How did this become
your concept, Ms. Billy?
You should've at least changed the name.
Excuse me, but what are you talking about?
I'm sorry, Camille,
you're finding out this way.
But really?
LoveFeast?
She stole that from LoveList.
Ms. Billy, what are you talking about?
I didn't steal anything!
That's my concept!
Ms. Camille, believe me.
I didn't steal anything.
- Stop, Abi.
- Ms. Billy, you stop!
Ms. Billy, you are my idol.
But don't take what's mine, Ms. Billy.
Make something of your own!
If you can't think of anything,
then I'm sorry,
but don't steal my concept, Ms. Billy.
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [GRUNTS]
[BLOW LANDS]
- Ow, Ms. Billy!
- Liar! Liar! Liar!
Liar! Liar!
[BILLY BREATHES SHAKILY]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Stop lying.
How did you get it?
I'm not lying, Ms. Billy.
- I didn't take anything from you.
- God, I thought you just had no choice.
That's why you had to lie
on your application.
But, guess what, Abi?
- You really are a liar.
- [CAMILLE] Abi.
- Is that true?
- Uh--
[BILLY] Camille, be careful with this one.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
She's a liar.
[ABI INHALES SHAKILY]
Ms. Camille, believe me.
I don't know what Ms. Billy is saying
because that is my concept!
- That's my idea.
- Enough, Abi. Enough.
- Enough with the drama!
- Ms. Billy!
I get it now! It's clear to me.
I now know what kind of person you are.
You made a choice.
You know this could turn
into a legal case, right?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You played with the wrong person.
You deceived me.
My company.
And I will make sure you face
the consequences.
Ms. Billy, please don't threaten me.
Oh, it's not a threat, Abi.
It's a promise.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
- [VALERIE] He's mine!
- Wow!
- [KEVIN] And I'm hers!
- They're official now!
A skirt? Does it really have
to be a skirt?
What straight man wears a skirt?
- [JORDAN CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
- Wait, I'll show you something.
Here, look. These are men.
Whatever. He's gay.
Why are you so affected?
Look at our boss. He doesn't care!
Boss.
You're not jealous anymore, are you?
We're done.
You're on your own.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Congrats! One rival officially eliminated!
[JORDAN CHUCKLES]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[ROBBIE] Oh, we're still closed!
[DOOR CREAKS OPEN]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Abi stole our entire presentation?
Yes. I saw the exact same sheets.
But how?
I don't know, but…
I sent the sheets to your email.
Maybe someone got hacked!
O-Or maybe someone leaked it?
Among us? That seems--
That seems impossible.
Who did you send the copies to?
To the three of you!
I didn't even send it to Valerie!
[TONI GASPS]
This is so stressful!
- My gosh!
- [LIGHTER CLICKING]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Fire alarm.
[MUSIC TURNS TENSE]
HIGH SCHOOL:
BAGONG SILANG HIGH SCHOOL
I can do many things.
Yeah, we heard.
When it comes to work, you can see
that I'm good, I'm smart.
- I'm resourceful.
- But your work isn't spotless.
You got caught, bro.
I would do anything for my mother.
I'm sorry. [INHALES]
That's why I played with fire.
Sorry.
Believe me, I can help you, sir.
I know a lot about POS!
I'm a computer expert, aren't I, boss?
Computer hacking.
You should just be a bouncer!
You punch pretty well.
Boss, I'll change.
I promise.
I just really need a job.
If you could please give me a chance.
[CALOY BREATHES SHAKILY]
I don't want to go back to my old ways.
I just really need--
I just really need medicine for my mother.
We may have reached a settlement,
but I still don't trust you.
You think I relaxed
after the hearing at the fiscal?
I didn't.
We did some digging.
And my lawyer discovered
that your mother's not sick.
She's been gone for a long time.
She left when you were still a child.
I-I don't know what you're saying.
Okay.
I can have you imprisoned again.
I said I don't know!
You have no right
to speak about my family.
You know, Caloy…
I'm also suspicious of your alibi
about LoveList's former employee.
No.
But one thing's for sure. I'll find out.
And I'll discover who your boss is.
[FOLDER THUDS]
I said I don't know
what you're talking about!
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CHAIR SLAMS]
[DOOR CREAKS OPEN, CLOSES]
I did apply to their company.
But it's not true that
I lied on my application.
To be honest,
I noticed a lot of shortcomings
in LoveList.
That's why I gave them
a lot of good suggestions.
LoveFeast was one of my suggestions!
They were so impressed by it!
That's why I thought
they were going to hire me.
But Ms. Billy rejected me.
Classic Billy. She's a thief.
We both ran for student council president
back in university.
I led the polls in the first two hours.
But she suddenly won!
Up to this day, I know it was rigged.
[ABI EXHALES]
I also felt that deceit.
But, Ms. Camille, I'm here…
[ABI GULPS, SNIFFLES]
…because my mom is sick.
I really need a job.
I said the same thing to Ms. Billy,
but she didn't care.
So I thought about where else to apply.
I thought of Pebblng.
That's why I stormed in earlier.
Because I really wanted to
present my idea to you.
Because I really need money.
I need a job to pay for
my mother's medical expenses.
Well, her loss is my gain.
Morrie, go ahead and orient her.
- Oh, orient as in…?
- As in, I am the boss.
I can hire instantly. Is there a problem?
Of course not.
All right.
Thank you so much, Ms. Camille!
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
I knew it!
What the…?
Did she steal my flash drive?!
That's why it was missing!
Chief!
We have to sue her!
We don't have enough proof!
Abi stealing it wasn't caught on cam.
But she triggered the fire alarm, right?
And you know what?
I think she didn't just steal LoveFeast.
What else did she steal?
My shoes.
[CHARM] Shoes?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MORRIE] So, this is the common area.
That's the pantry.
- Uh…
- [TELEPHONE RINGING]
Complete your requirements,
and I'll send you a list.
[CHUCKLING, INHALES SHARPLY]
[SIGHS]
[CHUCKLING SOFTLY]
Oh!
I'm sorry.
I'm…
[SNIFFLES]
I'm just happy I finally have a job.
These are tears of joy.
- [ABI SNIFFLES]
- Okay.
Why is it called Pebblng?
You don't know why?
I'll do my research.
No, let me.
Pebblng a dating trend
inspired by penguins.
It's lovers giving each other
tokens of affection.
Like pebbles. Do you get it?
Absolutely.
I knew what it meant.
I thought there was a more…
you know, deeper meaning to it.
Anyway, standard requirements.
NDA. Background check.
No posting. No leaking.
What you see here stays here.
- Okay?
- Mm-hmm.
Anyway, I'll leave you to it.
- I'll be right here.
- All right, thank you.
[SIGHS]
[RAIN] Robbie?
- [ROBBIE] Yeah?
- Bill out for table five.
- [ROBBIE] Got it. Hold on.
- [PLATES CLATTERING]
I remember seeing Abi when I got home.
Ms. Billy!
- [DOOR SLAMS]
- [ABI] Hello!
Abi!
I went to the center earlier.
What for?
She kept bugging Auntie Pres.
She insisted on wanting to thank me.
And then the next day,
I lost my house keys.
I immediately had our lock changed.
Auntie, did you see
my keys here last night?
My shoes also went missing.
Auntie, have you seen my red shoes?
The pair I wore
to the LoveList anniversary party.
She was wearing
the exact shoes in Pebblng.
Dude.
That's creepy.
But there's no way to tell
if those were really mine.
I doubt it, though. It's the same pair.
Am I being petty for making
an issue out of my shoes?
Not really.
I'm more worried about you.
If she really did steal those
from your house…
then Abi is dangerous, dude.
I didn't know she was that bad.
We already lost an investor,
and we're also being accused of copying.
Okay, so Abi
planned all of this.
She pretended to be your friend
to have access to you.
To get info?
Maybe Camille sent her.
Like a mole. A spy.
Anyway.
Don't worry about Caloy.
I told you.
I can handle him.
I'm not done with Abi.
I just need a favor, please, dude.
Anything.
Boss.
That's a lot.
Still looking into Abi?
Billy went through a lot because of her.
She'll get through it.
Of course, 'cause you're there for her.
Same for her.
She's always there for me too.
Right.
No matter what bad luck comes your way,
you're both lucky.
Lucky in what sense?
You both have each other.
Ride or die, right?
- Cheers.
Girls, I'm so sorry.
I know it's the weekend.
But we need to have a meeting tomorrow.
Oh.
What time?
[BILLY] 10:00 a.m.
We need to do some damage control.
You already know what happened
with Ms. Lindsay.
We can't afford to lose
our other investors.
Ah, okay.
We need to come up with
a better plan than LoveFeast.
So what now?
We're moving on from LoveFeast?
We shouldn't just let that Abi
get away with it, right?
Chief, will you really let it slide?
Of course not.
Let's discuss our next move tomorrow.
All right. See you tomorrow.
Okay. Thanks, chief.
Okay. Bye.
HOW WE WENT SILENT
BY BAYANI ROBLES
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[YANI] Okay!
Last two, love!
Oh, okay.
I told you I could
bring them to the gallery.
It's okay, love. I'll go with you.
- [THUDS]
- I can handle it.
Look at you.
I know you're tired.
Not really.
You know what?
Let's just meet at 10:00 a.m.
I'll be there by eight
because of how excited I am.
And it's been so long
since I've had my own exhibit.
But
I can feel it in my bones
that this will be my best series yet.
That's why I'm sure
that we'll make a lot of sales.
It's because I'm with my lucky charm!
[SMOOCHES, HUFFS]
And, of course,
this will surely be added
to our wedding budget.
- Right?
- Mm-hmm. [CHUCKLES]
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES, FADES]
I tried applying to Jordan's bar
to scope things out quickly.
But I got pissed off.
C'mon, Caloy.
- What did you expect?
- He kept talking about me!
I thought I already fooled him
during the hearing.
Turns out, he's still set
on putting me in jail.
Ah, they're really best friends.
Billy said the same thing.
"You better meet with your lawyers."
Fine. She can do her worst.
She has no idea that I can do worse.
[CHUCKLES]
What are we going to do, 'Bi? [SIGHS]
This.
What's in that?
A lot of things.
Even the list of investors is in here.
Billy said I was a thief.
[SCOFFS]
But she's the original thief herself!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- You're just the same.
- You're right!
We'll play then.
We'll play a game of tag.
- You're so bold.
- Go home!
Don't I get a cup of coffee?
I'll just use the bathroom.
- Stop!
- I need to pee.
You need to go home.
You're so stubborn, Caloy.
I've told you so many times
that we shouldn't meet.
But you won't listen!
Starting today, we really shouldn't meet!
I can't do that.
You know I can't leave you alone.
- Abi…
- You're such a flirt!
We're partners, right?
We should stick together.
C'mon, you don't need to play hard to get.
Fine.
I'll do anything.
I'll apologize to Jordan
even if I don't want to.
For you.
Do you really think he'll trust you?
I'll find a way!
I've been doing everything
for you, haven't I?
I'll do anything for you. C'mon!
You even look beautiful today.
- C'mon--
- Let go of her!
- Let go!
- Go home. Now.
Caloy, go home. Now!
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[NOTIFICATION CHIMES]
[JORDAN] Don't worry, dude…
Abi won't get away with this.
[BILLY] She really won't, dude.
Thanks.
[UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES]
You're bringing men here?
You're such a flirt!
That's your boyfriend!
Will you get fooled by a man too?
Didn't you learn from
your father's mistakes?
You'll turn out just like him!
He'll eventually leave you too!
What?
You're so…
You might end up leaving me!
He's not my boyfriend.
[MARIELA] That's exactly what
your father said to me.
He always denied it when I asked,
but the truth is, he was cheating on me!
You are all cheaters! Cheaters!
I am not like him!
I am not like my father!
Do you understand?
And, Ma,
when did I ever leave you?
I never left you, haven't I?
I'm not dating around. I'm working!
I've got a new job.
Didn't I tell you about it this morning?
I'll be earning more.
I'm doing this for us!
I want you to be proud of me.
Just like how proud you are of Abi!
- Where are you working?
- You don't need to know.
All I know is…
All I know is that our lives
will be better again.
[SIGHS]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING, FADES]
- Billy.
- Aunt Pres.
- Here are the files you asked for on Abi.
- Thank you.
Is this the only record
she has in Angels of Grace?
Yes. Just that.
She wrote a different address
on her resumé
when she applied to LoveList.
She's giving fake addresses.
Could she also be lying about her mother?
I'll find something I can use
against this woman.
[PRECIOUS] Billy,
if your suspicions are right,
maybe you should stay away from her.
She's dangerous, Billy.
[BILLY] If we let it slide,
then she'll do it again.
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
I taught Oliver to fight back
when he was being wronged.
Lead by example, Aunt Pres.
But this is a different issue!
That's the thing. This is worse!
That's why she should pay for it.
Are you going to get even?
I'm not getting even, Aunt Pres.
It's collecting a debt.
We lost so much
when she stole that project.
She even went inside our house!
We're not sure about that.
But what if she was the one who went in?
You and Oliver could've gotten hurt!
I won't let that slide.
She messed with the wrong person.
[TENSE MUSIC BUILDS, THEN FADES]
- Precious?
- Brandon?
[BRANDON]
What a coincidence!
[OLIVER]
It was a giddy smile.
- [BILLY] Who is this man you're with?
- [OLIVER] That's Sir Eric.
[BILLY] I remember this.
She said she owns an internet cafe.
Where are you taking
my computers?!
[CHARM] How did you get
our files on LoveFeast?
Let go of her!
[ABI] Find that computer, okay?
Every single picture and video
on it has to be deleted!
[JORDAN] Where are you going?!
- [BOTH GRUNTING]
- [CALOY] Come on, hit me!
- How can I support you today?
- I'm Melissa.
I'm having second thoughts
about my wedding.
My dad doesn't approve of him.
[JORDAN] You need this.
You make it look so easy.
Being strong. Composed.
I could say the same to you.
Oh, very good!
- What's this?
- A friendship song.
- [SINGING] ♪ Just lean on me ♪
- [GUITAR STRUMMING]
♪ Let's just dance to the beat
Of our hearts ♪
♪ Just lean on me ♪
♪ When you're crying ♪